http://www.leaderpromos.com/leader/privacy-policy.jsf

We are OPEN during COVID-19!
X
We use cookies to give you the best possible experience. By continuing to use this site you agree to our use of cookies. Our cookies don't collect personal information. For more information, please read our privacy policy.
Close
Idea Board
My Account
Idea Board
Browse Products
Apparel
Bags & Totes
Tech Items
About Leaderpromos
Close collaboration with you and your team is what sets us apart from being just another promotional products company. Leveraging our knowledge of your business, we're able to create world-class promotional solutions that incorporate more than just another branded product. We create solutions that work with a proven ROI!
SIGN-UP
Privacy Policy
Call Us Now 1-877-677-9988
My Account
Idea Board
Sample Bag
Cart
The Leader Difference
Item Added
Welcome to your personal Idea Board. Simply drag and drop items that you love onto your board to share, order samples or print. Sign in or register to save your board.
Sign in
or
register
to save your board.
Close
Select All
ShareRequest SampleSave
Start saving your favorite products to your Idea Board!
Delete selected items from Idea Board
Delete ItemsCancel
The Leader Difference
Company Web Stores
RFP & Procurement
National Programs
Overseas Sourcing
Blog
Welcome to Leaderpromos.com (the "Website").
We understand that privacy online is important to users of our Website, especially when conducting business. This statement governs our privacy policies with respect to those users of the Website ("Visitors") who visit without transacting business and Visitors who register to transact business on the Website and make use of the various services offered by Leaderpromos.com (collectively, "Services") ("Authorized Customers").
Personally Identifiable Information
“Personally Identifiable Information" refers to any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains, including, but not limited to, name, address, phone number, fax number, email address, financial profiles, social security number, and credit card information. Personally Identifiable Information does not include information that is collected anonymously (that is, without identification of the individual user) or demographic information not connected to an identified individual.
What Personally Identifiable Information is collected?
We may collect basic user profile information from all of our Visitors. We collect the following additional information from our Authorized Customers: the names, addresses, phone numbers and email addresses of Authorized Customers, the nature and size of the business, and the nature and size of the advertising inventory that the Authorized Customer intends to purchase or sell.
What organizations are collecting the information?
In addition to our direct collection of information, our third party service vendors (such as credit card companies, clearinghouses and banks) who may provide such services as credit, insurance, and escrow services may collect this information from our Visitors and Authorized Customers. We do not control how these third parties use such information, but we do ask them to disclose how they use personal information provided to them from Visitors and Authorized Customers. Some of these third parties may be intermediaries that act solely as links in the distribution chain, and do not store, retain, or use the information given to them.
How does the Website use Personally Identifiable Information?
We use Personally Identifiable Information to customize the Website, to make appropriate service offerings, and to fulfill buying and selling requests on the Website. We may email Visitors and Authorized Customers about research or purchase and selling opportunities on the Website or information related to the subject matter of the Website. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to contact Visitors and Authorized Customers in response to specific inquiries, or to provide requested information.
With whom may the information may be shared?
Personally Identifiable Information about Authorized Customers may be shared with other Authorized Customers who wish to evaluate potential transactions with other Authorized Customers. We may share aggregated information about our Visitors, including the demographics of our Visitors and Authorized Customers, with our affiliated agencies and third party vendors. We also offer the opportunity to "opt out" of receiving information or being contacted by us or by any agency acting on our behalf.
How is Personally Identifiable Information stored?
Personally Identifiable Information collected by Leaderpromos.com is securely stored and is not accessible to third parties or employees of Leaderpromos.com except for use as indicated above.
What choices are available to Visitors regarding collection, use and distribution of the information?
Visitors and Authorized Customers may opt out of receiving unsolicited information from or being contacted by us and/or our vendors and affiliated agencies by responding to emails as instructed, or by contacting us at:
Account@Leaderpromos.com
Are Cookies Used on the Website?
Cookies are used for a variety of reasons. We use Cookies to obtain information about the preferences of our Visitors and the services they select. We also use Cookies for security purposes to protect our Authorized Customers. For example, if an Authorized Customer is logged on and the Website is unused for more than 10 minutes, we will automatically log the Authorized Customer off.
How does Leaderpromos.com use login information?
Leaderpromos.com uses login information, including, but not limited to, IP addresses, ISPs, and browser types, to analyze trends, administer the Website, track a user's movement and use, and gather broad demographic information.
What partners or service providers have access to Personally Identifiable Information from Visitors and/or Authorized Customers on the Website?
Leaderpromos.com has entered into and will continue to enter into partnerships and other affiliations with a number of vendors.
Such vendors may have access to certain Personally Identifiable Information on a need to know basis for evaluating Authorized Customers for service eligibility.
Our privacy policy does not cover their collection or use of this information.
Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information to comply with law. We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information in order to comply with a court order or subpoena or a request from a law enforcement agency to release information. We will also disclose Personally Identifiable Information when reasonably necessary to protect the safety of our Visitors and Authorized Customers.
How does the Website keep Personally Identifiable Information secure?
All of our employees are familiar with our security policy and practices. The Personally Identifiable Information of our Visitors and Authorized Customers is only accessible to a limited number of qualified employees who are given a password in order to gain access to the information. We audit our security systems and processes on a regular basis. Sensitive information, such as credit card numbers or social security numbers, is protected by encryption protocols, in place to protect information sent over the Internet. While we take commercially reasonable measures to maintain a secure Website, electronic communications and databases are subject to errors, tampering and break-ins, and we cannot guarantee or warrant that such events will not take place and we will not be liable to Visitors or Authorized Customers for any such occurrences.
How can Visitors correct any inaccuracies in Personally Identifiable Information?
Visitors and Authorized Customers may contact us to update Personally Identifiable Information about them or to correct any inaccuracies by emailing us at:
Account@Leaderpromos.com
Can a Visitor delete or deactivate Personally Identifiable Information collected by the Website?
We provide Visitors and Authorized Customers with a mechanism to delete/deactivate Personally Identifiable Information from the Site's database by contacting Support@Leaderpromos.com. However, because of backups and records of deletions, it may be impossible to delete a Visitor's entry without retaining some residual information. An individual who requests to have Personally Identifiable Information deactivated will have this information functionally deleted, and we will not sell, transfer, or use
Personally Identifiable Information relating to that individual in any way moving forward.
What happens if the Privacy Policy Changes?
We will let our Visitors and Authorized Customers know about changes to our privacy policy by posting such changes on the Website. However, if we are changing our privacy policy in a manner that might cause disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information that a Visitor or Authorized Customer has previously requested not be disclosed, we will contact such Visitor or Authorized Customer to allow such Visitor or Authorized Customer to prevent such disclosure.
Links
This Website contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another web Website. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policies may differ from ours.
© 2019
Leaderpromos.com
All rights reserved.
Unauthorized duplication or publication of any materials from this Website is expressly prohibited.
Need help finding just the right product? We're here to help!
